Blades, Rubén. Rubén Blades recordings and papers: Guide AWM Spec Coll 100
Eda Kuhn Loeb Music Library
- Series XI. Music and lyrics, 2 boxes; 2 boxes.
  - Subseries 1. General music and lyrics, Box 1.
    - Folder with enlarged lyrics for use in concert and set list, Date unknown
  - Subseries 2. Song lyrics and translations donated by Paula Campbell, Box 1.
    Included here are handwritten and typed song lyrics by Rubén Blades
    - Paula C lyrics
      Handwritten original by Rubén Blades, lyrics translated by Blades into English
    - El Cantante lyrics
      Handwritten original by Rubén Blades
    - Pablo Pueblo lyrics
    - La Doña, El Viejo Da Silva, The Burial, Maestra Vida lyrics
      Handwritten original translations by Rubén Blades
    - Maestra Vida I and II lyrics
      Complete translations by Rubén Blades (typed, photocopies, with some corrections; 18 pages, includes a synopsis of the music of both parts, a story told in salsa music).
  - Subseries 3. Oversized music and lyrics, Box 2.
    - Woody Guthrie estate, lyrics and correspondence
    - Oversized music and lyrics, 1 folder.
- Series XII. Acting documents, 1987-2013; 2 boxes; 2 boxes.
  - Subseries 1. General acting files, Box 1.
    - Acting Awards, 1 folder.
    - Call Sheets, 1 folder.
    - H.B.O., 1 folder.
    - Robert Mugge, Mug-Shot Productions, 1 folder.
    - Screen Actors Guild Arbitration, 1995; 1 folder.
    - Buscando Guayabas (film project), 1988; 1 folder.
    - Chinese Box (film), 1997; 1 folder.
    - Cipriano Armenteros (film), 2009; 1 folder.
    - Color of Night (film), 1994; 1 folder.
    - The Counselor (film), 2013; 1 folder.
    - Cradle Will Rock (film), 1999; 1 folder.
    - Crazy From The Heart (film), 1991; 1 folder.
    - Dead Man Out (film), 1989; 1 folder.
    - Josephine Baker Story (film), 1991; 1 folder.
    - Maybe Havana (film), 1 folder.
    - Milagro Beanfield War (film), 1988; 1 folder.
    - Miracle on I-880 (film), 1993; 1 folder.
    - Taina (film), 2000; 1 folder.
    - Untitled Project by Lois Berge, 1998; 1 folder.
    - Script Notes, Unidentified, 1 folder.
  - Subseries 2. Materials relating to The Capeman, Box 2.
    Documents related to Blades participation in the 1998 Broadway musical by Paul Simon and Derek Walcott
    - Capeman Correspondence, 1 folder.
    - Capeman Song Lists, 1 folder.
    - Capeman Contact Sheet, 1 folder.
    - Capeman Press, 2 folders.
    - Capeman Music, 1 folder.
    - Salvador Agrón, Writings, and Press Clippings, 1 folder.
    - Casting - Workshop Cast, 1 folder.
    - Casting - Casting Lists (old), 1 folder.
    - Casting - Cast, Boys, 1 folder.
    - Casting - To Be Offered, Men, 1 folder.
    - Casting - Cut, Audition, 1 folder.
    - Casting - General, 3 folders.
    - Capeman Rehearsal Script, 1996-10-31; 1 folder.
    - Capeman Script
      With handwritten notes
- Series XIII. Scripts and production notes, 1983-2012; 4 boxes; 4 boxes.
  Predominantly related to acting roles portrayed by Blades. Arranged alphabetically.
  - All the Pretty Horses, 1 folder.
  - Anywhere But Here, 1 folder.
  - Archelon, 1 folder.
  - Behind the Eight Ball, 1 folder.
  - Bringing Out the Dead, 1 folder.
  - Buscando Guayabas, 1 folder.
  - Captain Starshine, 1 folder.
  - Chinese Box, 1 folder.
  - Chocolat, 1 folder.
  - Clandestino, 1 folder.
  - Cradle Will Rock, 4 folders.
  - Creencias, 1 folder.
  - Critical Condition, 1 folder.
  - Crazy From the Heart, 1 folder.
  - Crossover Dreams, 3 folders.
  - A Dancer's Leap, 1 folder.
  - Dead Man Out, 2 folders.
  - Dear America, 1 folder.
  - The Devil's Own, 1 folder.
  - Diva, 1 folder.
  - Do the Right Thing, 1 folder.
  - Empire, 1 folder.
  - Falls Road, 1 folder.
  - Fatal Beauty, 1 folder.
  - For the Love of the Game, 1 folder.
  - Gideon's Crossing, 9 folders.
  - Gladiator, 1 folder.
  - The Good Soldier, 1 folder.
  - Heart of the Deal, 1 folder.
  - A Heartwarming Adventure, 1 folder.
  - Humboldt Park, 1 folder.
  - The Huntsmen, 1 folder.
  - Jinetera, 1 folder.
  - Josephine Baker Story, 2 folders.
  - The Last Fight, 1 folder.
  - The Lemon Sisters, 1 folder.
  - Maestra Vida, 1 folder.
  - The Maldonado Miracle, 1 folder.
  - Milagro, 1 folder.
  - The Milagro Beanfield War, 2 folders.
  - Mission to Mars, 1 folder.
  - Mo' Better Blue, 1 folder.
  - No Man's Journey, 1 folder.
  - Nydia's Chuletas, 1 folder.
  - Once In The Life, 1 folder.
  - Once Upon a Time in Mexico, 3 folders.
  - One Man's War, 1 folder.
  - The Other Side, 1 folder.
  - The Pianist, 1 folder.
  - A Place Where the Sea Remembers, 1 folder.
  - Preacher, 1 folder.
  - Predator 2, 1 folder.
  - The Red Weather, 1 folder.
  - Rocky and Diego, 1 folder.
  - Rubirosa, 1 folder.
  - Safe House, 1 folder.
  - Scorpion Spring, 1 folder.
  - Sins of the City, 1 folder.
  - Spin, 2 folders.
  - Some of My Best Friends, 1 folder.
  - The Song the Killed the Snake, 1 folder.
  - Spoken Word, 1 folder.
  - Starry Night, 1 folder.
  - The Strongman, 2 folders.
  - Sultan, 1 folder.
  - The Super, 1 folder.
  - Swag, aka Ryan's Rules, 1 folder.
  - Tailor of Panama, 1 folder.
  - The Two Jakes, 1 folder.
  - La Verdadura Historia de Pedro Navaja, 1 folder.
  - Un Vietnam en Cada Ghetto, 1 folder.
  - Waiting for Salazar, 2 folders.
  - The X-Files, 1 folder.
- Series XIV. Business and financial documents, 1970s-2000s; 5 boxes; 5 boxes.
  - Subseries 1. Business correspondence, Box 1.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1988-1990; 2 folders.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1991; 2 folders.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1992; 3 folders.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1993; 2 folders.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1994.; 1 folder.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1995; 1 folder.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1998; 1 folder.
    - Shustek (Jerry Shustek Correspondence), 1999; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1984; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1988-1990; 2 folders.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1991; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1992; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1993; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1994; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1995; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1998; 1 folder.
    - Stollman (Norman Stollman Correspondence), 1 folder.
    - Pinos (Jorge Pinos)/William Morris Correspondence, 1992; 3 folders.
    - Pinos (Jorge Pinos)/William Morris Correspondence, 1993; 2 folders.
    - Nordstrom (Cristina Nordstrom), 1998; 1 folder.
    - Brezner (Larry Brezner), 1998; 1 folder.
    - Publishing Letters, 1986-2001; 2 folders.
    - Lyon and Lyon - Bankruptcy Filing, 1 folder.
    - Philips Chilena, 1 folder.
    - Eric Osvaldo/Latitude 47, 1 folder.
    - Deborah Castillero, 1 folder.
    - Fax Journals, 1991-1995; 1 folder.
    - Two letters concerning Empire soundtrack
      1. Typed letter from RB to David Fritz 12/9/2001 re: publishing, with notes 2. Letter to David Fritz from intern re: Empire soundtrack
  - Subseries 2. Contracts and negotiations, Boxes 2-3.
    - Contracts and Negotiations, 8 folders.
    - Folder with multiple folders re: booking, contracts, 1989-1993
    - Sony, 1998; 2 folders.
    - Warner Chappell Agreements, 1 folder.
    - Sessions at W. 54th Contract, 1 folder.
    - Concert Contracts, 2002; 17 folders.
      - Jackie Gleason Theater, Miami Beach, FL, 2002-10-12; 1 folders
      - Tampa Bay Performing Arts Center, Tampa, FL, 2002-10-13; 1 folders
      - House of Blues, New Orleans, LA, 2002-10-15; 1 folders
      - Verizon Vireless Theater, Houston, TX, 2002-10-16; 1 folders
      - La Zona Rosa, Austin TX, 2002-10-17; 1 folders
      - El Rey Theater, Albuquerque, NM, 2002-10-19; 1 folders
      - Abraham Chavez Theater, El Paso, TX, 2002-10-20; 1 folders
      - The Lensic Theater, Santa Fe, NM, 2002-10-21; 1 folders
      - Mayan Theater, Los Angeles, CA, 2002-10-24; 1 folders
      - San Francisco Jazz Festival, San Francisco, CA, 2002-10-25; 1 folders
      - Copacabana, New York, NY, 2002-11-15; 1 folders
      - Garde Arts Center, New London, CT, 2002-11-16; 1 folders
      - Berklee Performance Center, Boston, MA, 2002-11-17; 1 folders
      - 9:30 Club, Washington, D.C., 2002-11-19; 1 folders
      - Hoyt Sherman Theater, Des Moines, IA, 2002-11-22; 1 folders
      - Orpheum, Madison, WI, 2002-11-23; 1 folders
      - The Pantages, Minneapolis, MN, 2002-11-24; 1 folders
    - Concert Contracts, 2008; 4 folders.
    - Softball Arena, Athens, Greece (CANCELLED), 2008-7-16; 1 folders
    - Tour of Italy: Milan, Rome, 2008-7-19-2008-7-21; 1 folders
    - The Melkweg, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 2008-7-22; 1 folders
    - Tour of Spain: Alicante, artagena, Madrid, Vlgo, Zorgoza, Tenerife, San Sebastian de la Gomez, Las Palmas de la Gran Canaria, Sant Feliu dels Guinols, 2008-7-24-2008-8-8; 1 folders
    - Budgets for recording Empire soundtrack, Mundo
  - Subseries 3. Legal documents, Box 4.
    - Legal Documents, 1970s; 1 folder.
    - Legal Documents, 1980s; 6 folders.
    - Legal Documents, 1990s; 2 folders.
    - Legal Documents, 2000s; 1 folder.
  - Subseries 4. Royalty statements, Box 5.
    Collection of Royalty Statements for Blades recordings beginning in the 1970s
  - Subseries 5. Financial documents, Box 6.
    - Bank Accounts, 1 folder.
    - Banking and Tax Preparation, 1 folder.
    - Student Loans, 1 folder.
    - Finances Scratch Notes, 1 folder.
    - Bills, 1 folder.
    - Budget for Panama Concert, 1999-12-31
eyJtZXRhZGF0YV9wcmVmaXgiOiJvYWlfZWFkIiwiZnJvbSI6IjIwMjMtMDQtMTMgMDA6MDA6MDAgVVRDIiwidW50aWwiOiIyMDIzLTA0LTE0IDA3OjAwOjA0IFVUQyIsInN0YXRlIjoicHJvZHVjaW5nX3JlY29yZHMiLCJsYXN0X2RlbGV0ZV9pZCI6MCwicmVtYWluaW5nX3R5cGVzIjp7IlJlc291cmNlIjo0NzI0fSwiaXNzdWVfdGltZSI6MTY4MTQ3ODk2OTQ1N30=